Register of the Vladimir Pribylovskiĭ collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Biographical sources for Russian politicians, 1989-2006
  - Kuz'min, Apollon Grigor'evich, 1991 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Labusov, Boris Nikolaevich, 1999 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Lakhova, Ekaterina Filippovna, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Lapshin, Mikhail Ivanovich, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Laptev, Ivan Dmitrievich, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Latsis, Otto Rudol'fovich, 1995 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Latyshev, Valerii, 1999 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Lavrov, Sergei Viktorovich, 1994 (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Lazutkin, Valentin Valentinovich, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Lebedev, Aleksandr Evgen'evich, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Lebedev, Igor' Vladimirovich, 2000 (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Lebedev, Iurii Mikhailovich, 2000 (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Lebed', Aleksandr Ivanovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 15: 3-8)
  - Lebed', Aleksei Ivanovich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Leonov, Leonid Maksimovich, 1994 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Leonov, Nikolai, 1993 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Leont'ev, Mikhail Vladimirovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Leont'ev, Viacheslav Petrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Lepekhin, Vladimir Anatol'evich, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Lerner, Grigorii L'vovich, 1997 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Lesin, Mikhail Iur'evich, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 15: 10)
  - Lesnevskaia, Irena (Iren) Stefanovna, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Leushkin, Aleksei Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Levashev (Levashov), Aleksei Vladimirovich, 1996 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Levitin, Mikhail, 1994 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Liatskii, Vladislav Borisovich, 1992 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Ligachev, Egor Kuz'mich, 1996 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Likhachev, Dmitrii Sergeevich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Likhachev, Vasilii Nikolaevich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Lilleviali, German Arvedovich, 1999 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Limonov (Savenko), Eduard Veniaminovich, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Lipatnikov, Iurii Vasil'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Lipitskii, Vasilii Semenovich, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 15: 12)
  - Lisichkin, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1996 (Box-folder 15: 12)
  - Lisin, Aleksandr Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Lisin, Vladimir Pavlovich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Lisinenko, Igor' Vasil'evich, 2000 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Lisitsyn, Anatolii Ivanovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Lisitsyn, Vladimir Pavlovich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Lisovskii, Sergei Fedorovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - List'ev, Vladislav Nikolaevich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Liubashevskii, Iurii Iakovlevich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Liubimov, Aleksandr Mikhailovich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Liubin, Viktor Petrovich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Livshits, Aleksandr Iakovlevich, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 15: 14)
  - Livshits, Vadim, 1993 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Lobov, Oleg Ivanovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Lobov, Vladimir Nikolaevich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Loginov, Andrei Viktorovich, 1997 (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - Logunov, Valentin Andreevich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - Lonovskikh, Anatolii Ivanovich, 1990 (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - Lopatin, Mikhail Aleksandrovich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - Lopatin, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - Lopukhin, Vladimir Mikhailovich, 1991 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Lozovoi, Vladimir Dem'ianovich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Lubenchenko, Konstantin Dmitrievich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Luchanskii, Grigorii Emmanuilovich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Luchin, Viktor Osipovich, 1996 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Luchinskii, Iurii Mikhailovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Lukin, Vladimir Petrovich, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Luk'ianov, Anatolii Ivanovich, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Luk'ianov, Mikhail Vladimirovich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Luzhkov, Iurii Mikhailovich, 1991-2006 (Box-folder 16: 5-11)
  - Lysenko, Nikolai Nikolaevich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 16: 12)
  - Lysenko, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 16: 12)
  - Lyzlov, Viacheslav Evgen'evich, 1990 (Box-folder 16: 12)
  - Magomaev, Muslim Magometovich, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Magomedov, Stanislav Iunusovich, 1996 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Makaranets, Boris Isakovich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Makarevich, Nikolai, circa 1992 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Makarov, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Makarov, Andrei Mikhailovich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Makarov, Nikolai Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Makashov, Al'bert Mikhailovich, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Makhachev, Gadzhi Nukhievich, 2000 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Makharadze, Maisarat, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Makharadze, Valerii Antonovich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Makhmudov, Iskander Kakhramonovich, 2000 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Maksimov, Vladimir Emel'ianovich, 1993 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Malashenko, Igor' Evgen'evich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Malei, Mikhail Dmitrievich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Maliarov, Igor' Olegovich, 1996 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Malinkovich, Vladimir Dmitrievich, 1997 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Malinovskii, Al'fred Avgustovich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Malkin, Anatolii Grigor'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Malkin, Evgenii Borisovich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Malykh, Pavel Valentinovich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Malyshev, Nikolai Grigor'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Mal'gin, Andrei Viktorovich, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Mal'tsev, Viacheslav, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Mamin, Iurii Borisovich, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Mamleev, Iurii Vital'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Mamut, Aleksandr Leonidovich, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Manannikov, Aleksei Petrovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Maniakin, Sergei Iosifovich, 1996 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Manokhin, Anatolii Nikolaevich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Marchuk, Gurii Ivanovich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Marenich, Iurii Iosifovich, 1992-1992 (Box-folder 17: 5)
  - Markidonov, Sergei Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 5)
  - Martynov, Evgenii, 1993 (Box-folder 17: 5)
  - Marychev, Viacheslav Antonovich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 17: 5)
  - Masarskii, Mark Leonidovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Mashinskii, Viktor Leonidovich, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Mashits, Vladimir Mikhailovich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Mashkov, Vitalii Vladimirovich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Masiuk, Elena Vladimirovna, 1997 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Maskhadov, Aslan Alievich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Masliukov, Iurii Dmitrievich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Matiukhin, Georgii Gavrilovich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Matochkin, Iurii Semenovich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Matvienko, Valentina Ivanovna, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 17: 7)
  - Mau, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 2000 (Box-folder 17: 7)
  - Mavrodi, Sergei Panteleevich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 17: 7)
  - Medvedev, Armen Nikolaevich, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Medvedev, Nikolai Pavlovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Medvedev, Pavel Alekseevich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Medvedev, Roi Aleksandrovich, 1991 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Medvedev, Sergei Konstantinovich, 1996 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Medvedev, Vadim Andreevich, 1990 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Medvedev, Vladimir Sergeevich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Medevdev, Zhores Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Medzhitova, El'mira, 1881 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Melik'ian, Gennadii Georgievich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Mel'nikov, Aleksei Iur'evich, 1996 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Men', Mikhail Aleksandrovich, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Men'shov, Vladimir Valentinovich, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Meshkov, Iurii Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Mezentsev, Vladimir Georgievich, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Miagkov, Petr Andreevich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Migranian, Adranik Movsesovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Mikhailov, Aleksandr Dmitrievich, 1994 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Mikhailov, Nikolai Vasil'evich, 1997 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Mikhailov, Sergei Anatol'evich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Mikhailov, Sergeii Andreevich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Mikhailov, Viacheslav Aleksandrovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Mikhailov, Viktor Nikitich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Mikhalkov, Nikita Sergeevich, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Mikheev, Valdimir Ivanovich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Mikitaev, Abdulakh Kasbulatovich, 1996 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Miliukov, Iurii Aleksandrovich, 1996 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Milonov, Vitalii Valentinovich, 1997 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Miloserdov, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Minin, Viktor, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Minkin, Aleksandr Viktorovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 17: 12)
  - Minzhurenko, Aleksandr Vasil'evich, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 17: 12)
  - Mironenko, Viktor Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 12)
  - Mironov, Boris Sergeevich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 17: 12)
  - Mironov, Oleg Orestovich, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 12)
  - Mironov, Sergei Mikhailovich, 2001 (Box-folder 17: 13)
  - Mironov, Sergei Pavlovich, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 13)
  - Mironov, Viktor Pimenovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 17: 13)
  - Mirzaianov, Vil Sultanovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 17: 13)
  - Mishin, Viktor Maksimovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 17: 13)
  - Mitina, Dar'ia Aleksandrovna, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 17: 14)
  - Mitiukov, Mikhail Alekseevich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 17: 14)
  - Mitkova, Tat'iana Rostislavovna, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 14)
  - Mizulina, Elena Borisovna, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 17: 14)
  - Mochaikin, Aleksandr Gennad'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Mogilevich, Semen Iur'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Mogutin, Iaroslav, 1999 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Moiseev, Boris Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Molostvov, Mikhail Aleksandrovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Monastyretskii, Valerii, 1997 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Monastyrskii, Mikhail L'vovich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Morokin, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Morozov, Igor' Nikolaevich, 1995 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Morozov, Oleg Viktorovich, 1999 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Moryzhenkov, Vladimir Alekseevich, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Moskovchenko, Nikolai Mikhailovich, 1992 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Moskvin, Iurii Nikolaevich, 1992 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Mostovoi, Petr Petrovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Mozgo, Igor' Nikolaevich, 1992 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Mozhaev, Boris Andreevich, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Mukha, Vitalii Petrovich, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 18: 3)
  - Mukhametshin, Farid Khairullovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 18: 3)
  - Mukusev, Vladimir Viktorovich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 18: 3)
  - Muladzhanov, Shod, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 3)
  - Muliukov, Marat Abdrasulovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 18: 3)
  - Murashev, Arkadii Nikolaevich, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 18: 4)
  - Murav'ev, Igor' Vladislavovich, 1990 (Box-folder 18: 5)
  - Murov, Evgenii Alekseevich, 2000 (Box-folder 18: 5)
  - Murzin, Dmitrii Aleksandrovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 18: 5)
  - Muzykantskii, Aleksandr Il'ich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 18: 5)
  - Nagibin, Iurii Markovich, 1994 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Naichukova, Svetlana Ivanovna, circa 1999 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Naishul', Vitalii Arkad'evich, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Nakonechnyi, Sergei, 1992 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Narusova, Liudmila Borisovna, 1999 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Nazarbaev, Nursultan Abishevich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Nazarchuk, Aleksandr Grigor'evich, 1996 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Nazdratenko, Evgenii Ivanovich, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 18: 7, Box-folder 54: 9)
  - Nechaev, Andrei Alekseevich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 18: 7)
  - Nechaev, Eduard Aleksandrovich, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 18: 8)
  - Nefedov, Evgenii, 1999 (Box-folder 18: 8)
  - Nekliudov, Igor', 1994 (Box-folder 18: 8)
  - Nekrasov, Biktor Romenovich, 1995 (Box-folder 18: 8)
  - Nekrasova, Marina, 1995 (Box-folder 18: 8)
  - Nemtsov, Boris Efimovich, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 18: 9-10)
  - Nesterov, Iurii Mikhailovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 18: 11)
  - Nesvizhskii, Vadim, circa 1995 (Box-folder 18: 11)
  - Neverov, Valerii Ivanovich, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 18: 11)
  - Nevzorov, Aleksandr Glebovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 18: 12)
  - Niiazov, Saparmurat Ataevich, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Nikishin, 1994 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Nikishkin, Grigorii Evgen'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Nikitin, Nikolai Stepanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Nikitin, Stanislav Georgievich, 1994 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Nikitin, Vladimir Stepanovich, 1996 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Nikitinskii, Leonid Vasil'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Nikolaev, Andrei Ivanovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Nikolaev, Mikhail Efimovich, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 18: 14)
  - Nikol'skii, Valerii Dmitrievich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 18: 14)
  - Nikonov, Viacheslav Alekseevich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Nikulin, Valerii Afanas'evich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Nishanov, Rafik Nishanovich, 1990 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Nisnevich, Iulii Anatol'evich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Norkin, Kemer Borisovich, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Nosov, Vavil Borisovich, 1991 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Nosovets, Sergei Anatol'evich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Notkin, Boris, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Novgorodtsev, Vsevolod Borisovich, 1995 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Novikov, Oleg Ivanovich, 1992 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Novitskii, Ivan Iur'evich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Novodvorskaia, Valeriia Il'inichna, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 19: 3)
  - Novoselov, Viktor Semenovich, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Novozhenov, Lev Iur'evich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Nozhikov, Iurii Abramovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Nozhnikov, Aleksandr Garrievich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Nuikin, Andrei Aleksandrovich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Nukhaev, Khozh-Akhmed, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Numerov, Nikolai Vladimirovich, 1995 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Nuriev, Boris, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Obolenski, Aleksandr Mitrofanovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Ochin, Boris Fedorovich, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Ogorodnikov, Aleksandr Ioil'evich, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Ogurtsov, Igor' Viacheslavovich, 1991 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Okudzhava, Bulat Shalvovich, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Oleinik, Boris Il'ich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Oligov (Olegov), Andrei Vladimirovich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Ol'shanskii, Dmitrii Vadimovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Onishchenko, Gennadii Grigor'evich, 1996 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Ordzhonikidze, Iosif Nikolaevich, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Orekhov, Ruslan Gennad'evich, 1997 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Oreshkin, Dmitrii, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Orlov, Aleksandr Sergeevich, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Orlov, Boris Sergeevich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Orlov, Iurii Fedorovich, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Orlov, Oleg Igorevich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Orlov, Viktor Petrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Orlova, Svetlana Iur'evna, 1998 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Osadchii, Igor' Vladimirovich, 1992 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Osipov, Iurii Sergeevich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Osipov, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Oskotskii, Valentin Dmitrievich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Osokin, Mikhail Glebovich, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Osovtsov, Aleksandr Avraamovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Oswald, Lee Harvey, 1995 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Ozerov, Viktor Alekseevich, 1995 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Ozov, Anatolii Galimzhanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Padva, Genrikh Pavlovich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Pain, Emil' Abramovich, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Pak, Zinovii Petrovich, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Palamarchuk, Petr Georgievich, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Palii, Viktor Osipovich, 1997 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Pamfilova, Ella Aleksandrovna, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 19: 10)
  - Panfilov, Anatolii, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Panich, Iulian, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Panikin, Aleksandr Stepanovich, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Panina, Elena Vladimirovna, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Pankin, Boris Dmitrievich, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Pankov, Anatolii Semenovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 19: 9)
  - Panskov, Vladimir Georgievich, 1997 (Box-folder 19: 9)
  - Paramonov, Mikhail Iur'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 10)
  - Paramonova, Tat'iana Vladimirovna, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 19: 10)
  - Parfenov, Leonid Gennad'evich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 19: 11)
  - Parfenov, Sergei Gennad'evich, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 19: 11)
  - Parfenov, Valerii Vital'evich, 1991 (Box-folder 19: 11)
  - Parkhaev, Evgenii Alekseevich, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 11)
  - Pastukhov, Boris Nikolaevich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - Patarkatsishvili, Badri Shalvovich, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - Pavlenko, Sergei Iur'evich, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - Pavlov, Anatolii Georgievich, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - Pavlov, Nikolai Aleksandrovich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - Pavlov, Valentin Sergeevich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - Pavlovskii, Gleb Olegovich, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - Pekarev, Vladimir Ianovich, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - Pereliakin, Aleksandr, 1995 (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - Perfil'ev, Valentin Viktorovich, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - Peskov, Iurii Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - Petrakov, Nikolai Iakovlevich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - Petrenko, Sergei Vasil'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 14)
  - Petrov, Iurii Vladimirovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 19: 14)
  - Petrov, Oleg Vadimovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 19: 15)
  - Petukhov, Iurii, circa 1993 (Box-folder 19: 15)
  - Petukhova, Marina Borisovna, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 15)
  - Piiasheva, Larisa Ivanovna, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 19: 15)
  - Pikhoia, Rudol'f Germanovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 19: 16)
  - Pilipchuk, Vladimir Il'ich, 1997 (Box-folder 19: 16)
  - Piorunskii, Dmitrii Aleksandrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 16)
  - Piotrovskii, Mikhail Borisovich, 1999 (Box-folder 19: 16)
  - Pisigin, Valerii Fridrikhovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 19: 16)
  - Pitirim (Konstantin Vladimirovich Nechaev), 1993 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - Platonov, Vladimir Mikhailovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - Platov, Vladimir Ignat'evich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - Pochinok, Aleksandr Petrovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 20: 2)
  - Podatev, Vladimir Petrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Podberezkin, Aleksei Ivanovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Podgornov, Nikolai Mikhailovich, 1999 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Podkolzin, Evgenii, 1995 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Podoprigora, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Podrabinek, Aleksandr Pinkhosovich, 1995 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Podshivalov, Igor' Iur'evich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Poegli, Vadim Iur'evich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Pokhmelkin, Viktor Valer'evich, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Pokrovskii, Valentin Ivanovich, 1994 (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Polevanov, Vladimir Pavlovich (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Poliakov, Iurii, 1997 (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - Politkovskii, Aleksandr Vladimirovich, 1995 (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - Pollyeva, Dzhakhan Redzhepovna, 1999 (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - Polosin, Viacheslav Sergeevich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - Polovets, Aleksandr, 1999 (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - Polozkov, Ivan Kuz'mich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - Polozov, Boris Gennad'evich, 1998 (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - Poltoranin, Mikhail Nikiforovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 20: 7)
  - Poluektov, Valentin Viktorovich, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Ponasov, Stepan Nikolaevich, 1996 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Ponidelko, Anatolii, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Ponomarev, Gennadii Semenovich, 1995 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Ponomarev, Lev Aleksandrovich, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Ponomarev, Mikhail, 1997 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Ponomareva, Kseniia Iur'evna, 1997 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Popkovich, Roman Semenovich, 1997 (Box-folder 20: 9)
  - Popov, Aleksandr Pavlovich, 1999 (Box-folder 20: 9)
  - Popov, Gavriil Kharitonovich, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 20: 10-12)
  - Popov, Iurii Iur'evich, circa 1996 (Box-folder 20: 13)
  - Popov, Mikhail Vasil'evich, 1990 (Box-folder 20: 13)
  - Popov, Oleg Georgievich, 1991 (Box-folder 20: 13)
  - Poptsov, Oleg Maksimovich, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 20: 13)
  - Porokhova, Valeriia Maksimovna, 1999 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Postychev, Vladimir Mikhailovich, 1997 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Posuvaliuk, Viktor Viktorovich, 1996 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Povoliaev, Vladimir Mitrofanovich, 1994 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Pozdyshev, Erik Nikolaevich, 1993 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Pozgalev, Viacheslav Evgen'evich, 1996 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Prelin, Igor' Nikolaevich, 1996 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Prigarin, Aleksei Alekseevich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Prigozhin, Arkadii Il'ich, 1992 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Prikhod'ko, Sergei Eduardovich, 1997 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Primakov, Evgenii Maksimovich, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 20: 15)
  - Pristavkin, Anatolii Ignat'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - Prokhanov, Aleksandr Andreevich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - Prokhorov, Viacheslav Aleksandrovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - Prokof'ev, Iurii Anatol'evich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - Prokopov, Fedor, 1995 (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - Prokop'ev, Leonid Prokop'evich, 1990 (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - Proshechkin, Evgenii Viktorovich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 20: 17)
  - Prusak, Mikhail Mikhailovich, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 20: 17)
  - Pugachev, Boris, 1993 (Box-folder 20: 17)
  - Pugin, Nikolai, 1995 (Box-folder 20: 17)
  - Putilov, Aleksandr Evgen'evich, 1997 (Box-folder 20: 17)
  - Putin, Vladimir Vladimirovich, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 21: 1-3)
  - Putina, Liudmila Aleksandrovna, 2001 (Box-folder 21: 4)
  - Puzanovskii, Andrian Georgievich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 21: 4)
  - Pykhtin, Sergei Petrovich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - P"etsukh, Viacheslav Alekseevich, 1993 (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - P'iankov, Boris, 1993 (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - Rachinskii, Ian, 1993 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Raduev, Salman, 1997 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Raikov, Gennadii Ivanovich, 2000 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Raikov, Vladimir, 1995 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Rakhimov, Murtaza Gubaidullovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Rakitov, Anatolii Il'ich, 1996 (Box-folder 21: 7)
  - Rakitskaia, Galina Iakovlevna, 1992 (Box-folder 21: 7)
  - Rasputin, Valentin Grigor'evich, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 21: 7)
  - Rastorguev, Valerii Nikolaevich, 1995 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Rastoshchenov, Mikhail Mikhailovich, circa 1990 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Razin, Andrei Aleksandrovich, 1996 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Rebrikov, Vladimir Andreevich, 1992 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Reiman, Leonid Dododzhonovich, 1999 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Remchukov, Konstantin Vadimovich, 1999 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Resin, Vladimir Iosifovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Reznik, Genri Markovich, 1997 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Riabov, Aleksandr Ivanovich, 1996 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Riabov, Nikolai Timofeevich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Riabov, Sergei Nikolaevich, 1995 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Riabtsev, Petr Zinov'evich, 1997 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Riazanov, El'dar Aleksandrovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Ridiger, Aleksei Mikhailovich (Aleksii II), 1992-1999 (Box-folder 21: 10)
  - Riumin, Valerii Vasil'evich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 21: 11)
  - Riurikov, Dmitrii Borisovich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 21: 11)
  - Rodionov, Igor' Nikolaevich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 21: 11)
  - Rodionov, Petr Ivanovich, 1996 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - Rodionov, Sergei Sergeevich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - Rodiushkin, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - Rogozin, Georgii Georgievich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - Roitman, Il'ia Borisovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 21: 12)